https://cvm.msu.edu/about/privacy-statement

Select
This online privacy statement is intended to inform you of the ways
in which cvm.msu.edu / animalhealth.msu.edu
(“Site”) collects
information, the uses to which that information will be put, and the
ways in which we protect information you choose to provide us.Please note that other Michigan State University websites may adopt different privacy practices as their specific needs require.Use of this Site is subject to all applicable state and federal laws, as well as general University policiesThis online privacy statement is intended to inform you of the ways
in which cvm.msu.edu / animalhealth.msu.edu
(“Site”) collects
information, the uses to which that information will be put, and the
ways in which we protect information you choose to provide us.Please note that other Michigan State University websites may adopt different privacy practices as their specific needs require.Use of this Site is subject to all applicable state and federal laws, as well as general University policies
Information Collected
This Site collects two general types of information: (a) information you
voluntarily provide to us, which may include personal information (such
as your name, address, e-mail address, etc.), and (b) information we
collect automatically when you visit this Site through cookies, third
party tracking technologies and server logs.
Information Voluntarily Provided by You
This Site will only collect personal information that you knowingly
and voluntarily provide by, for example, responding to surveys,
completing membership forms, sending e-mails, etc.
It is this Site’s
general practice to use personal information only for the purposes for
which it was requested and any additional uses specifically stated on
the Site.
However, information collected through this Site may be
subject to the University’s obligation to respond to subpoenas, court
orders, discovery requests, and requests for public records under the
Michigan Freedom of Information Act.
Further, the disclosure of
information collected through this Site is subject to the provisions of
the Family Educational Rights & Privacy Act.The University may also access or permit access to information
collected through this Site in accordance with and subject to the
limitations of the University’s Acceptable Use Policy for Information
Technology Resources.Although this Site has security measures in place to protect personal
information provided to us by users, users should also take steps to
protect personal information by, for example, closing all web browsers
after using the Site.
Updating Personal Information
You may correct, update, or remove the personal information provided to us through the use of the Site. In particular:To correct, update, or remove your personal information on cvm.msu.edu / animalhealth.msu.edu, please email us at communications@cvm.msu.edu.
Information We Collect Automatically
This Site collects information automatically through the use of
cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs.
This
information does not include any personal information.
We use this
information primarily to monitor the use of this Site and to make
improvements.
We may share this data with partners in order to enhance
the functionality of this Site.Cookies“Cookies” are small text files used to collect information about
website activity.
No personal information is collected through our use
of cookies.
This Site uses cookies for two main purposes: (a) to carry
information about your current session at this Site from one web page to
the next, which also allows you to automatically login to other
Michigan State University websites, and (b) to identify you on this Site
on return visits.You have the option of disabling or not accepting cookies by changing
the preferences on your browser.
If you opt to disable cookies, you
will still be able to use certain sections of our Site. However, you
will not be able to use any parts of this Site that require a login
(e.g. accessing secured content, posting to message boards, etc.).Third Party Tracking TechnologyThis Site uses a tracking technology called Google Analytics to
obtain Site usage information such as users’ Internet Protocol (IP)
addresses, Internet domain and host names, browser software, and the
date and time that the Site is visited.
Data obtained through Google
Analytics does not include and is not linked to any personal
information.
Data from Google Analytics allows us to monitor the use of
this Site, understand how users find our Site, and improve the Site’s
function and content.Site usage data collected through Google Analytics is not shared with
other Google products and tools.
Our use of Google Analytics is in
compliance with Google’s Terms of Service and the MSU Access to Student
Information Guidelines.
Google provides more information about Google’s
privacy practices and information on how to opt-out of Google Analytics
tracking of your web browsing.You may also wish to review the MSU Access to Student Information Guidelines.Server LogsOur web servers routinely generate logs that contain the following types of information each time the Site is used:The date, time and length of your visit.The path taken through our Site and the browser being used.The list of files downloaded and the amount of time spent viewing video or audio files.The IP Address of the computer accessing our Site.Any errors encountered.This information is used primarily to monitor the functioning and integrity of the Site and other MSU websites.
Links
This Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we do
not control or claim any responsibility for the privacy practices or
content of such other sites. We encourage users to read the privacy
statements of each website they visit.
If we make changes to our privacy statement, we will indicate this on our home page.
Disclaimer
Neither Michigan State University, nor any of its units, programs,
employees, agents or individual trustees, shall be liable for any
improper or incorrect use of information obtained through the use of
this Site.
Consent
By using this Site you consent to the terms of this privacy statement.
Questions and feedback
Your questions, comments and concerns are always welcome.
Please send
us your feedback regarding the privacy statement or any other issues at:
communications@cvm.msu.edu.
Happy 2020 Holidays from the MSU College of Veterinary Medicine
Happy 2020 Holidays from the MSU Veterinary Diagnostic Laboratory
What is a Veterinary Nurse?
Dual-degree Program at the MSU College of Veterinary Medicine
Undergraduate Student Summer Research Program in Biomedical Sciences
Why Join SAVMA?
Equine Fellows Summer Program with Dr. Duncan Peters and Dr. Lori Bidwell
Equine Analysis Systems 2016 Fellowship Summary
Equine Fellows Experience: Equine Athlete with Dr. Brad Hill
Bovine Health Management for Early-Career Rural Veterinarians, Online Distance Education
What is BAS?
What is NTUAS?
International Surgical Training Scholar: Small Animal Surgery
Thank you for the generous support to McPhail Equine Performance Center provided by
National and Canadian Research Opportunities for Veterinary Students
Opportunities for Summer Research for DVM Students at US Institutions
MSU
Boehringer Ingelheim (legacy Merial) Veterinary Scholars Program
National Veterinary Scholars Symposia
NIH T35 Veterinary Scholars Program
Special MSU Endowed Summer Research Fellowships
Boehringer Ingelheim (legacy Merial) Scholars National Website
Morris Animal Foundation Summer Research Fellowships
Fellowships and Externships in Lab Animal Medicine
BRUSH Summer Research Program for Students Underrepresented in Biomedical Sciences
Where do our BRUSH scholars come from?
What’s next for BRUSH program alumni?
Who Are the Members of My Animal's Veterinary Health Team?
Expand
What is a veterinary specialist?
In Vivo Evaluation of Lag Screw Fixation of Sacroiliac Luxation/Fracture
Integrative Medicine (Acupuncture)
Hyperthyroidism and Iodine (I131)
Hyperthyroidism and Iodine (I131)
Related Sites:
Hospital
VDL
